0	1	Senate	Senate	NNP	dep	469	ORGANIZATION	 (X (NNP Senate)	1
0	2	Passes	pass	VBZ	dep	469	O	 (VBZ Passes)	1
0	3	Coburn	Coburn	NNP	dep	469	PERSON	 (NNP Coburn)	1
0	4	Obama	Obama	NNP	dep	469	PERSON	 (NNP Obama)	1
0	5	Bill	Bill	NNP	dep	469	PERSON	 (NNP Bill)	1
0	6	to	to	TO	dep	469	O	 (TO to)	1
0	7	Create	create	VB	dep	469	ORGANIZATION	 (VB Create)	1
0	8	Internet	Internet	NNP	dep	469	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Internet)	1
0	9	Database	Database	NNP	dep	469	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Database)	1
0	10	of	of	IN	dep	469	ORGANIZATION	 (IN of)	1
0	11	Federal	Federal	NNP	dep	469	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Federal)	1
0	12	Spending	spend	VBG	dep	469	ORGANIZATION	 (VBG Spending)	1
0	13	U	U	NNP	dep	469	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP U)	1
0	14	S	S	NNP	dep	469	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP S)	1
0	15	Senator	Senator	NNP	dep	469	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Senator)	1
0	16	Barack	Barack	NNP	dep	469	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Barack)	1
0	17	Obama	Obama	NNP	dep	469	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Obama)	1
0	18	Barack	Barack	NNP	dep	469	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Barack)	1
0	19	Obama	Obama	NNP	dep	469	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Obama)	1
0	20	Senate	Senate	NNP	dep	469	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Senate)	1
0	21	Passes	pass	VBZ	dep	469	O	 (VBZ Passes)	1
0	22	Coburn	Coburn	NNP	dep	469	PERSON	 (NNP Coburn)	1
0	23	Obama	Obama	NNP	dep	469	PERSON	 (NNP Obama)	1
0	24	Bill	Bill	NNP	dep	469	PERSON	 (NNP Bill)	1
0	25	to	to	TO	dep	469	O	 (TO to)	1
0	26	Create	create	VB	dep	469	ORGANIZATION	 (VB Create)	1
0	27	Internet	Internet	NNP	dep	469	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Internet)	1
0	28	Database	Database	NNP	dep	469	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Database)	1
0	29	of	of	IN	dep	469	ORGANIZATION	 (IN of)	1
0	30	Federal	Federal	NNP	dep	469	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Federal)	1
0	31	Spending	spend	VBG	dep	469	ORGANIZATION	 (VBG Spending)	1
0	32	Friday	Friday	NNP	dep	469	DATE	 (NNP Friday)	1
0	33	September	September	NNP	dep	469	DATE	 (NNP September)	1
0	34	8	8	CD	dep	469	DATE	 (CD 8)	1
0	35	2006	2006	CD	dep	469	DATE	 (CD 2006)	1
0	36	FOR	for	IN	dep	469	O	 (IN FOR)	1
0	37	IMMEDIATE	immediate	JJ	dep	469	O	 (JJ IMMEDIATE)	1
0	38	RELEASE	release	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN RELEASE)	1
0	39	Obama	Obama	NNP	dep	469	O	 (NNP Obama)	1
0	40	Contact	contact	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN Contact)	1
0	41	Tommy	Tommy	NNP	dep	469	PERSON	 (NNP Tommy)	1
0	42	Vietor	Vietor	NNP	dep	469	PERSON	 (NNP Vietor)	1
0	43	or	or	CC	cc	469	O	 (CC or)	1
0	44	Robert	Robert	NNP	dep	469	PERSON	 (NNP Robert)	1
0	45	Gibbs	Gibbs	NNP	dep	469	PERSON	 (NNP Gibbs)	1
0	46	202	202	CD	dep	469	NUMBER	 (CD 202)	1
0	47	228	228	CD	dep	469	NUMBER	 (CD 228)	1
0	48	5511	5511	CD	dep	469	DATE	 (CD 5511)	1
0	49	Coburn	Coburn	NNP	dep	469	O	 (NNP Coburn)	1
0	50	Contact	contact	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN Contact)	1
0	51	John	John	NNP	dep	469	PERSON	 (NNP John)	1
0	52	Hart	Hart	NNP	dep	469	PERSON	 (NNP Hart)	1
0	53	202	202	CD	dep	469	NUMBER	 (CD 202)	1
0	54	228	228	CD	dep	469	NUMBER	 (CD 228)	1
0	55	5357	5357	CD	dep	469	NUMBER	 (CD 5357)	1
0	56	Date	Date	NNP	dep	469	O	 (NNP Date)	1
0	57	September	September	NNP	dep	469	DATE	 (NNP September)	1
0	58	8	8	CD	dep	469	DATE	 (CD 8)	1
0	59	2006	2006	CD	dep	469	DATE	 (CD 2006)	1
0	60	Senate	Senate	NNP	dep	469	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Senate)	1
0	61	Passes	pass	VBZ	dep	469	O	 (VBZ Passes)	1
0	62	Coburn	Coburn	NNP	dep	469	PERSON	 (NNP Coburn)	1
0	63	Obama	Obama	NNP	dep	469	PERSON	 (NNP Obama)	1
0	64	Bill	Bill	NNP	dep	469	PERSON	 (NNP Bill)	1
0	65	to	to	TO	dep	469	O	 (TO to)	1
0	66	Create	create	VB	dep	469	O	 (VB Create)	1
0	67	Internet	Internet	NNP	dep	469	O	 (NNP Internet)	1
0	68	Database	Database	NNP	dep	469	O	 (NNP Database)	1
0	69	of	of	IN	dep	469	O	 (IN of)	1
0	70	Federal	Federal	NNP	dep	469	O	 (NNP Federal)	1
0	71	Spending	spend	VBG	dep	469	O	 (VBG Spending)	1
0	72	WASHINGTON	WASHINGTON	NNP	dep	469	LOCATION	 (NNP WASHINGTON)	1
0	73	U	U	NNP	dep	469	O	 (NNP U)	1
0	74	S	S	NNP	dep	469	O	 (NNP S)	1
0	75	Senators	Senators	NNPS	dep	469	O	 (NNPS Senators)	1
0	76	Barack	Barack	NNP	dep	469	PERSON	 (NNP Barack)	1
0	77	Obama	Obama	NNP	dep	469	PERSON	 (NNP Obama)	1
0	78	D	D	NNP	dep	469	PERSON	 (NNP D)	1
0	79	IL	il	NN	dep	469	PERSON	 (NN IL)	1
0	80	and	and	CC	cc	469	O	 (CC and)	1
0	81	Tom	Tom	NNP	dep	469	PERSON	 (NNP Tom)	1
0	82	Coburn	Coburn	NNP	dep	469	PERSON	 (NNP Coburn)	1
0	83	R	R	NNP	dep	469	O	 (NNP R)	1
0	84	OK	ok	UH	dep	469	O	 (UH OK)	1
0	85	today	today	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN today)	1
0	86	hailed	hail	VBD	dep	469	O	 (VBD hailed)	1
0	87	the	the	DT	dep	469	O	 (DT the)	1
0	88	Senate	Senate	NNP	dep	469	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Senate)	1
0	89	s	s	VBZ	dep	469	O	 (VBZ s)	1
0	90	passage	passage	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN passage)	1
0	91	of	of	IN	dep	469	O	 (IN of)	1
0	92	the	the	DT	dep	469	O	 (DT the)	1
0	93	Federal	Federal	NNP	dep	469	O	 (NNP Federal)	1
0	94	Funding	Funding	NNP	dep	469	O	 (NNP Funding)	1
0	95	Accountability	Accountability	NNP	dep	469	O	 (NNP Accountability)	1
0	96	and	and	CC	cc	469	O	 (CC and)	1
0	97	Transparency	Transparency	NNP	dep	469	O	 (NNP Transparency)	1
0	98	Act	Act	NNP	dep	469	O	 (NNP Act)	1
0	99	a	a	DT	dep	469	O	 (DT a)	1
0	100	bill	bill	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN bill)	1
0	101	that	that	WDT	dep	469	O	 (WDT that)	2
0	102	will	will	MD	dep	469	O	 (MD will)	2
0	103	create	create	VB	dep	469	O	 (VB create)	2
0	104	a	a	DT	dep	469	O	 (DT a)	2
0	105	Google	Google	NNP	dep	469	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Google)	2
0	106	like	like	IN	dep	469	O	 (IN like)	2
0	107	search	search	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN search)	2
0	108	engine	engine	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN engine)	2
0	109	and	and	CC	cc	469	O	 (CC and)	2
0	110	database	database	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN database)	2
0	111	to	to	TO	dep	469	O	 (TO to)	2
0	112	track	track	VB	dep	469	O	 (VB track)	2
0	113	approximately	approximately	RB	dep	469	O	 (RB approximately)	2
0	114	1	1	CD	dep	469	NUMBER	 (CD 1)	2
0	115	trillion	trillion	CD	dep	469	NUMBER	 (CD trillion)	2
0	116	in	in	IN	dep	469	O	 (IN in)	2
0	117	federal	federal	JJ	dep	469	O	 (JJ federal)	2
0	118	grants	grant	NNS	dep	469	O	 (NNS grants)	2
0	119	contracts	contract	NNS	dep	469	O	 (NNS contracts)	2
0	120	earmarks	earmark	NNS	dep	469	O	 (NNS earmarks)	2
0	121	and	and	CC	cc	469	O	 (CC and)	2
0	122	loans	loan	NNS	dep	469	O	 (NNS loans)	2
0	123	By	by	IN	dep	469	O	 (IN By)	2
0	124	helping	help	VBG	dep	469	O	 (VBG helping)	2
0	125	to	to	TO	dep	469	O	 (TO to)	2
0	126	lift	lift	VB	dep	469	O	 (VB lift)	2
0	127	the	the	DT	dep	469	O	 (DT the)	2
0	128	veil	veil	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN veil)	2
0	129	of	of	IN	dep	469	O	 (IN of)	2
0	130	secrecy	secrecy	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN secrecy)	2
0	131	in	in	IN	dep	469	O	 (IN in)	2
0	132	Washington	Washington	NNP	dep	469	LOCATION	 (NNP Washington)	2
0	133	this	this	DT	dep	469	O	 (DT this)	2
0	134	database	database	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN database)	2
0	135	will	will	MD	dep	469	O	 (MD will)	2
0	136	help	help	VB	dep	469	O	 (VB help)	2
0	137	make	make	VB	dep	469	O	 (VB make)	2
0	138	us	we	PRP	dep	469	O	 (PRP us)	2
0	139	better	better	JJR	dep	469	O	 (JJR better)	2
0	140	legislators	legislator	NNS	dep	469	O	 (NNS legislators)	2
0	141	reporters	reporter	NNS	dep	469	O	 (NNS reporters)	2
0	142	better	better	JJR	dep	469	O	 (JJR better)	2
0	143	journalists	journalist	NNS	dep	469	O	 (NNS journalists)	2
0	144	and	and	CC	cc	469	O	 (CC and)	2
0	145	voters	voter	NNS	dep	469	O	 (NNS voters)	2
0	146	more	more	RBR	dep	469	O	 (RBR more)	2
0	147	active	active	JJ	dep	469	O	 (JJ active)	2
0	148	citizens	citizen	NNS	dep	469	O	 (NNS citizens)	2
0	149	Obama	Obama	NNP	dep	469	PERSON	 (NNP Obama)	2
0	150	said	say	VBD	dep	469	O	 (VBD said)	2
0	151	It	it	PRP	dep	469	O	 (PRP It)	3
0	152	s	s	VBZ	dep	469	O	 (VBZ s)	3
0	153	both	both	DT	dep	469	O	 (DT both)	3
0	154	unusual	unusual	JJ	dep	469	O	 (JJ unusual)	3
0	155	and	and	CC	cc	469	O	 (CC and)	3
0	156	encouraging	encouraging	JJ	dep	469	O	 (JJ encouraging)	3
0	157	to	to	TO	dep	469	O	 (TO to)	3
0	158	see	see	VB	dep	469	O	 (VB see)	3
0	159	interest	interest	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN interest)	3
0	160	groups	group	NNS	dep	469	O	 (NNS groups)	3
0	161	and	and	CC	cc	469	O	 (CC and)	3
0	162	bloggers	blogger	NNS	dep	469	O	 (NNS bloggers)	3
0	163	on	on	IN	dep	469	O	 (IN on)	3
0	164	the	the	DT	dep	469	O	 (DT the)	3
0	165	left	left	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN left)	3
0	166	and	and	CC	cc	469	O	 (CC and)	3
0	167	the	the	DT	dep	469	O	 (DT the)	3
0	168	right	right	JJ	dep	469	O	 (JJ right)	3
0	169	come	come	VBN	dep	469	O	 (VBN come)	3
0	170	together	together	RB	dep	469	O	 (RB together)	3
0	171	to	to	TO	dep	469	O	 (TO to)	4
0	172	achieve	achieve	VB	dep	469	O	 (VB achieve)	4
0	173	results	result	NNS	dep	469	O	 (NNS results)	4
0	174	This	this	DT	dep	469	O	 (DT This)	4
0	175	powerful	powerful	JJ	dep	469	O	 (JJ powerful)	4
0	176	grassroots	grassroot	NNS	dep	469	O	 (NNS grassroots)	4
0	177	alliance	alliance	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN alliance)	4
0	178	shows	show	VBZ	dep	469	O	 (VBZ shows)	4
0	179	that	that	IN	dep	469	O	 (IN that)	4
0	180	at	at	IN	dep	469	O	 (IN at)	4
0	181	the	the	DT	dep	469	O	 (DT the)	4
0	182	end	end	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN end)	4
0	183	of	of	IN	dep	469	O	 (IN of)	4
0	184	the	the	DT	dep	469	O	 (DT the)	4
0	185	day	day	NN	dep	469	TIME	 (NN day)	4
0	186	Americans	Americans	NNPS	dep	469	MISC	 (NNPS Americans)	4
0	187	want	want	VBP	dep	469	O	 (VBP want)	4
0	188	to	to	TO	dep	469	O	 (TO to)	4
0	189	see	see	VB	dep	469	O	 (VB see)	4
0	190	Congress	Congress	NNP	dep	469	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Congress)	4
0	191	work	work	VB	dep	469	O	 (VB work)	4
0	192	together	together	RB	dep	469	O	 (RB together)	4
0	193	to	to	TO	dep	469	O	 (TO to)	5
0	194	get	get	VB	dep	469	O	 (VB get)	5
0	195	something	something	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN something)	5
0	196	done	do	VBN	dep	469	O	 (VBN done)	5
0	197	and	and	CC	cc	469	O	 (CC and)	5
0	198	not	not	RB	dep	469	O	 (RB not)	5
0	199	continue	continue	VB	dep	469	O	 (VB continue)	5
0	200	to	to	TO	dep	469	O	 (TO to)	5
0	201	engage	engage	VB	dep	469	O	 (VB engage)	5
0	202	in	in	IN	dep	469	O	 (IN in)	5
0	203	the	the	DT	dep	469	O	 (DT the)	5
0	204	partisan	partisan	JJ	dep	469	O	 (JJ partisan)	5
0	205	gridlock	gridlock	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN gridlock)	5
0	206	that	that	WDT	dep	469	O	 (WDT that)	6
0	207	so	so	RB	dep	469	O	 (RB so)	6
0	208	often	often	RB	dep	469	O	 (RB often)	6
0	209	brings	bring	VBZ	dep	469	O	 (VBZ brings)	6
0	210	Capitol	Capitol	NNP	dep	469	LOCATION	 (NNP Capitol)	6
0	211	Hill	Hill	NNP	dep	469	LOCATION	 (NNP Hill)	6
0	212	to	to	TO	dep	469	O	 (TO to)	6
0	213	a	a	DT	dep	469	O	 (DT a)	6
0	214	grinding	grind	VBG	dep	469	O	 (VBG grinding)	6
0	215	halt	halt	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN halt)	6
0	216	Every	every	DT	dep	469	O	 (DT Every)	6
0	217	American	American	NNP	dep	469	MISC	 (NNP American)	6
0	218	has	have	VBZ	dep	469	O	 (VBZ has)	6
0	219	the	the	DT	dep	469	O	 (DT the)	6
0	220	right	right	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN right)	6
0	221	to	to	TO	dep	469	O	 (TO to)	6
0	222	know	know	VB	dep	469	O	 (VB know)	6
0	223	how	how	WRB	dep	469	O	 (WRB how)	7
0	224	their	they	PRP$	dep	469	O	 (PRP$ their)	7
0	225	government	government	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN government)	7
0	226	spends	spend	VBZ	dep	469	O	 (VBZ spends)	7
0	227	their	they	PRP$	dep	469	O	 (PRP$ their)	7
0	228	money	money	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN money)	7
0	229	and	and	CC	cc	469	O	 (CC and)	7
0	230	then	then	RB	dep	469	O	 (RB then)	7
0	231	to	to	TO	dep	469	O	 (TO to)	7
0	232	hold	hold	VB	dep	469	O	 (VB hold)	7
0	233	elected	elect	VBN	dep	469	O	 (VBN elected)	7
0	234	officials	official	NNS	dep	469	O	 (NNS officials)	7
0	235	accountable	accountable	JJ	dep	469	O	 (JJ accountable)	7
0	236	for	for	IN	dep	469	O	 (IN for)	7
0	237	those	those	DT	dep	469	O	 (DT those)	7
0	238	decisions	decision	NNS	dep	469	O	 (NNS decisions)	7
0	239	I	I	PRP	dep	469	O	 (PRP I)	7
0	240	applaud	applaud	VBP	dep	469	O	 (VBP applaud)	7
0	241	my	my	PRP$	dep	469	O	 (PRP$ my)	7
0	242	colleagues	colleague	NNS	dep	469	O	 (NNS colleagues)	7
0	243	for	for	IN	dep	469	O	 (IN for)	7
0	244	unanimously	unanimously	RB	dep	469	O	 (RB unanimously)	7
0	245	supporting	support	VBG	dep	469	O	 (VBG supporting)	7
0	246	a	a	DT	dep	469	O	 (DT a)	7
0	247	bill	bill	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN bill)	7
0	248	that	that	WDT	dep	469	O	 (WDT that)	8
0	249	will	will	MD	dep	469	O	 (MD will)	8
0	250	aid	aid	VB	dep	469	O	 (VB aid)	8
0	251	the	the	DT	dep	469	O	 (DT the)	8
0	252	American	american	JJ	dep	469	MISC	 (JJ American)	8
0	253	people	people	NNS	dep	469	O	 (NNS people)	8
0	254	in	in	IN	dep	469	O	 (IN in)	8
0	255	that	that	DT	dep	469	O	 (DT that)	8
0	256	effort	effort	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN effort)	8
0	257	Dr	Dr	NNP	dep	469	O	 (NNP Dr)	8
0	258	Coburn	Coburn	NNP	dep	469	PERSON	 (NNP Coburn)	8
0	259	said	say	VBD	dep	469	O	 (VBD said)	8
0	260	This	this	DT	dep	469	O	 (DT This)	9
0	261	bill	bill	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN bill)	9
0	262	is	be	VBZ	dep	469	O	 (VBZ is)	9
0	263	a	a	DT	dep	469	O	 (DT a)	9
0	264	small	small	JJ	dep	469	O	 (JJ small)	9
0	265	but	but	CC	cc	469	O	 (CC but)	10
0	266	significant	significant	JJ	dep	469	O	 (JJ significant)	10
0	267	step	step	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN step)	10
0	268	toward	toward	IN	dep	469	O	 (IN toward)	10
0	269	changing	change	VBG	dep	469	O	 (VBG changing)	10
0	270	the	the	DT	dep	469	O	 (DT the)	10
0	271	culture	culture	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN culture)	10
0	272	in	in	IN	dep	469	O	 (IN in)	10
0	273	Washington	Washington	NNP	dep	469	LOCATION	 (NNP Washington)	10
0	274	Only	only	RB	dep	469	O	 (RB Only)	10
0	275	by	by	IN	dep	469	O	 (IN by)	10
0	276	fostering	foster	VBG	dep	469	O	 (VBG fostering)	10
0	277	a	a	DT	dep	469	O	 (DT a)	10
0	278	culture	culture	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN culture)	10
0	279	of	of	IN	dep	469	O	 (IN of)	10
0	280	openness	openness	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN openness)	10
0	281	transparency	transparency	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN transparency)	10
0	282	and	and	CC	cc	469	O	 (CC and)	10
0	283	accountability	accountability	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN accountability)	10
0	284	will	will	MD	dep	469	O	 (MD will)	10
0	285	Congress	Congress	NNP	dep	469	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Congress)	10
0	286	come	come	VBN	dep	469	O	 (VBN come)	10
0	287	together	together	RB	dep	469	O	 (RB together)	10
0	288	to	to	TO	dep	469	O	 (TO to)	11
0	289	address	address	VB	dep	469	O	 (VB address)	11
0	290	the	the	DT	dep	469	O	 (DT the)	11
0	291	mounting	mount	VBG	dep	469	O	 (VBG mounting)	11
0	292	fiscal	fiscal	JJ	dep	469	O	 (JJ fiscal)	11
0	293	challenges	challenge	NNS	dep	469	O	 (NNS challenges)	11
0	294	that	that	IN	dep	469	O	 (IN that)	11
0	295	threaten	threaten	VBP	dep	469	O	 (VBP threaten)	11
0	296	our	we	PRP$	dep	469	O	 (PRP$ our)	11
0	297	future	future	JJ	dep	469	O	 (JJ future)	11
0	298	prosperity	prosperity	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN prosperity)	11
0	299	The	the	DT	dep	469	O	 (DT The)	11
0	300	group	group	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN group)	11
0	301	that	that	WDT	dep	469	O	 (WDT that)	12
0	302	deserves	deserve	VBZ	dep	469	O	 (VBZ deserves)	12
0	303	credit	credit	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN credit)	12
0	304	for	for	IN	dep	469	O	 (IN for)	12
0	305	passing	pass	VBG	dep	469	O	 (VBG passing)	12
0	306	this	this	DT	dep	469	O	 (DT this)	12
0	307	bill	bill	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN bill)	12
0	308	however	however	RB	dep	469	O	 (RB however)	12
0	309	is	be	VBZ	dep	469	O	 (VBZ is)	12
0	310	not	not	RB	dep	469	O	 (RB not)	12
0	311	Congress	Congress	NNP	dep	469	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Congress)	12
0	312	but	but	CC	cc	469	O	 (CC but)	12
0	313	the	the	DT	dep	469	O	 (DT the)	12
0	314	army	army	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN army)	12
0	315	of	of	IN	dep	469	O	 (IN of)	12
0	316	bloggers	blogger	NNS	dep	469	O	 (NNS bloggers)	12
0	317	and	and	CC	cc	469	O	 (CC and)	12
0	318	concerned	concerned	JJ	dep	469	O	 (JJ concerned)	12
0	319	citizens	citizen	NNS	dep	469	O	 (NNS citizens)	12
0	320	who	who	WP	dep	469	O	 (WP who)	13
0	321	told	tell	VBD	dep	469	O	 (VBD told)	13
0	322	Congress	Congress	NNP	dep	469	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Congress)	13
0	323	that	that	IN	dep	469	O	 (IN that)	13
0	324	transparency	transparency	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN transparency)	13
0	325	is	be	VBZ	dep	469	O	 (VBZ is)	13
0	326	a	a	DT	dep	469	O	 (DT a)	13
0	327	just	just	RB	dep	469	O	 (RB just)	13
0	328	demand	demand	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN demand)	13
0	329	for	for	IN	dep	469	O	 (IN for)	13
0	330	all	all	DT	dep	469	O	 (DT all)	13
0	331	citizens	citizen	NNS	dep	469	O	 (NNS citizens)	13
0	332	not	not	RB	dep	469	O	 (RB not)	13
0	333	a	a	DT	dep	469	O	 (DT a)	13
0	334	special	special	JJ	dep	469	O	 (JJ special)	13
0	335	privilege	privilege	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN privilege)	13
0	336	for	for	IN	dep	469	O	 (IN for)	13
0	337	political	political	JJ	dep	469	O	 (JJ political)	13
0	338	insiders	insider	NNS	dep	469	O	 (NNS insiders)	13
0	339	Their	they	PRP$	dep	469	O	 (PRP$ Their)	13
0	340	remarkable	remarkable	JJ	dep	469	O	 (JJ remarkable)	13
0	341	effort	effort	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN effort)	13
0	342	demonstrates	demonstrate	VBZ	dep	469	O	 (VBZ demonstrates)	13
0	343	that	that	IN	dep	469	O	 (IN that)	13
0	344	our	we	PRP$	dep	469	O	 (PRP$ our)	13
0	345	system	system	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN system)	13
0	346	of	of	IN	dep	469	O	 (IN of)	13
0	347	government	government	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN government)	13
0	348	does	do	VBZ	dep	469	O	 (VBZ does)	13
0	349	work	work	VB	dep	469	O	 (VB work)	13
0	350	when	when	WRB	dep	469	O	 (WRB when)	14
0	351	the	the	DT	dep	469	O	 (DT the)	14
0	352	people	people	NNS	dep	469	O	 (NNS people)	14
0	353	take	take	VBP	dep	469	O	 (VBP take)	14
0	354	the	the	DT	dep	469	O	 (DT the)	14
0	355	reins	rein	NNS	dep	469	O	 (NNS reins)	14
0	356	of	of	IN	dep	469	O	 (IN of)	14
0	357	government	government	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN government)	14
0	358	and	and	CC	cc	469	O	 (CC and)	14
0	359	demand	demand	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN demand)	14
0	360	change	change	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN change)	14
0	361	Dr	Dr	NNP	dep	469	O	 (NNP Dr)	14
0	362	Coburn	Coburn	NNP	dep	469	PERSON	 (NNP Coburn)	14
0	363	said	say	VBD	dep	469	O	 (VBD said)	14
0	364	More	more	JJR	dep	469	O	 (JJR More)	14
0	365	than	than	IN	dep	469	O	 (IN than)	14
0	366	100	100	CD	dep	469	NUMBER	 (CD 100)	14
0	367	organizations	organization	NNS	dep	469	O	 (NNS organizations)	14
0	368	ranging	range	VBG	dep	469	O	 (VBG ranging)	14
0	369	from	from	IN	dep	469	O	 (IN from)	14
0	370	Americans	Americans	NNPS	dep	469	MISC	 (NNPS Americans)	14
0	371	for	for	IN	dep	469	O	 (IN for)	14
0	372	Prosperity	Prosperity	NNP	dep	469	O	 (NNP Prosperity)	14
0	373	and	and	CC	cc	469	O	 (CC and)	14
0	374	Taxpayers	Taxpayers	NNPS	dep	469	O	 (NNPS Taxpayers)	14
0	375	for	for	IN	dep	469	O	 (IN for)	14
0	376	Common	common	JJ	dep	469	O	 (JJ Common)	14
0	377	Sense	sense	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN Sense)	14
0	378	to	to	TO	dep	469	O	 (TO to)	14
0	379	the	the	DT	dep	469	O	 (DT the)	14
0	380	National	National	NNP	dep	469	O	 (NNP National)	14
0	381	Gay	gay	NNS	dep	469	O	 (NNS Gay)	14
0	382	and	and	CC	cc	469	O	 (CC and)	14
0	383	Lesbian	lesbian	JJ	dep	469	O	 (JJ Lesbian)	14
0	384	Task	Task	NNP	dep	469	O	 (NNP Task)	14
0	385	Force	Force	NNP	dep	469	O	 (NNP Force)	14
0	386	and	and	CC	cc	469	O	 (CC and)	14
0	387	Greenpeace	Greenpeace	NNP	dep	469	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Greenpeace)	14
0	388	have	have	VBP	dep	469	O	 (VBP have)	14
0	389	endorsed	endorse	VBN	dep	469	O	 (VBN endorsed)	14
0	390	S	s	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN S)	14
0	391	2590	2590	CD	dep	469	DATE	 (CD 2590)	14
0	392	Dozens	dozen	NNS	dep	469	O	 (NNS Dozens)	14
0	393	of	of	IN	dep	469	O	 (IN of)	14
0	394	editorials	editorial	NNS	dep	469	O	 (NNS editorials)	14
0	395	boards	board	NNS	dep	469	O	 (NNS boards)	14
0	396	across	across	IN	dep	469	O	 (IN across)	14
0	397	the	the	DT	dep	469	O	 (DT the)	14
0	398	country	country	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN country)	14
0	399	including	include	VBG	dep	469	O	 (VBG including)	14
0	400	the	the	DT	dep	469	O	 (DT the)	14
0	401	Wall	Wall	NNP	dep	469	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Wall)	14
0	402	Street	Street	NNP	dep	469	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Street)	14
0	403	Journal	Journal	NNP	dep	469	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Journal)	14
0	404	Los	Los	NNP	dep	469	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Los)	14
0	405	Angeles	Angeles	NNP	dep	469	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Angeles)	14
0	406	Times	Times	NNP	dep	469	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Times)	14
0	407	Washington	Washington	NNP	dep	469	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Washington)	14
0	408	Post	Post	NNP	dep	469	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Post)	14
0	409	Chicago	Chicago	NNP	dep	469	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Chicago)	14
0	410	Sun	Sun	NNP	dep	469	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Sun)	14
0	411	Times	Times	NNP	dep	469	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Times)	14
0	412	and	and	CC	cc	469	O	 (CC and)	14
0	413	The	the	DT	dep	469	O	 (DT The)	14
0	414	Oklahoman	Oklahoman	NNP	dep	469	O	 (NNP Oklahoman)	14
0	415	have	have	VBP	dep	469	O	 (VBP have)	14
0	416	also	also	RB	dep	469	O	 (RB also)	14
0	417	endorsed	endorse	VBN	dep	469	O	 (VBN endorsed)	14
0	418	S	s	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN S)	14
0	419	2590	2590	CD	dep	469	DATE	 (CD 2590)	14
0	420	Forty	forty	CD	dep	469	NUMBER	 (CD Forty)	14
0	421	three	three	CD	dep	469	NUMBER	 (CD three)	14
0	422	Senators	senator	NNS	dep	469	O	 (NNS Senators)	14
0	423	co	co	VBP	dep	469	O	 (VBP co)	14
0	424	sponsored	sponsor	VBN	dep	469	O	 (VBN sponsored)	14
0	425	S	s	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN S)	14
0	426	2590	2590	CD	dep	469	DATE	 (CD 2590)	14
0	427	including	include	VBG	dep	469	O	 (VBG including)	14
0	428	Senate	Senate	NNP	dep	469	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Senate)	14
0	429	Majority	Majority	NNP	dep	469	O	 (NNP Majority)	14
0	430	Leader	Leader	NNP	dep	469	O	 (NNP Leader)	14
0	431	Bill	Bill	NNP	dep	469	PERSON	 (NNP Bill)	14
0	432	Frist	Frist	NNP	dep	469	PERSON	 (NNP Frist)	14
0	433	R	R	NNP	dep	469	O	 (NNP R)	14
0	434	TN	tn	NN	dep	469	ORGANIZATION	 (NN TN)	14
0	435	Senate	Senate	NNP	dep	469	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Senate)	14
0	436	Minority	Minority	NNP	dep	469	O	 (NNP Minority)	14
0	437	Leader	Leader	NNP	dep	469	O	 (NNP Leader)	14
0	438	Harry	Harry	NNP	dep	469	PERSON	 (NNP Harry)	14
0	439	Reid	Reid	NNP	dep	469	PERSON	 (NNP Reid)	14
0	440	D	D	NNP	dep	469	O	 (NNP D)	14
0	441	NV	NV	NNP	dep	469	O	 (NNP NV)	14
0	442	Tom	Tom	NNP	dep	469	PERSON	 (NNP Tom)	14
0	443	Carper	Carper	NNP	dep	469	PERSON	 (NNP Carper)	14
0	444	D	D	NNP	dep	469	O	 (NNP D)	14
0	445	DE	de	NN	dep	469	O	 (NN DE)	14
0	446	Susan	Susan	NNP	dep	469	PERSON	 (NNP Susan)	14
0	447	Collins	Collins	NNP	dep	469	PERSON	 (NNP Collins)	14
0	448	R	R	NNP	dep	469	O	 (NNP R)	14
0	449	ME	ME	NNP	dep	469	O	 (NNP ME)	14
0	450	Joe	Joe	NNP	dep	469	PERSON	 (NNP Joe)	14
0	451	Lieberman	Lieberman	NNP	dep	469	PERSON	 (NNP Lieberman)	14
0	452	D	D	NNP	dep	469	O	 (NNP D)	14
0	453	CT	CT	NNP	dep	469	O	 (NNP CT)	14
0	454	John	John	NNP	dep	469	PERSON	 (NNP John)	14
0	455	McCain	McCain	NNP	dep	469	PERSON	 (NNP McCain)	14
0	456	R	R	NNP	dep	469	PERSON	 (NNP R)	14
0	457	AZ	AZ	NNP	dep	469	PERSON	 (NNP AZ)	14
0	458	Hillary	Hillary	NNP	dep	469	PERSON	 (NNP Hillary)	14
0	459	Clinton	Clinton	NNP	dep	469	PERSON	 (NNP Clinton)	14
0	460	D	D	NNP	dep	469	O	 (NNP D)	14
0	461	NY	NY	NNP	dep	469	O	 (NNP NY)	14
0	462	John	John	NNP	dep	469	PERSON	 (NNP John)	14
0	463	Kerry	Kerry	NNP	dep	469	PERSON	 (NNP Kerry)	14
0	464	D	D	NNP	dep	469	PERSON	 (NNP D)	14
0	465	MA	MA	NNP	dep	469	PERSON	 (NNP MA)	14
0	466	John	John	NNP	dep	469	PERSON	 (NNP John)	14
0	467	Cornyn	Cornyn	NNP	dep	469	PERSON	 (NNP Cornyn)	14
0	468	R	R	NNP	dep	469	O	 (NNP R)	14
0	469	TX	TX	NNP	root	0	O	 (NNP TX)	14
0	470	and	and	CC	cc	469	O	 (CC and)	14
0	471	others	other	NNS	dep	469	O	 (NNS others))	14

