0	1	Revised	revise	VBN	dep	356	O	 (X (VBN Revised)	1
0	2	Schedule	schedule	VB	dep	356	O	 (VB Schedule)	1
0	3	for	for	IN	dep	356	O	 (IN for)	1
0	4	Obama	Obama	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Obama)	1
0	5	Downstate	Downstate	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Downstate)	1
0	6	Town	Town	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Town)	1
0	7	Hall	Hall	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Hall)	1
0	8	Tour	Tour	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Tour)	1
0	9	U	U	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP U)	1
0	10	S	S	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP S)	1
0	11	Senator	Senator	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP Senator)	1
0	12	Barack	Barack	NNP	dep	356	PERSON	 (NNP Barack)	1
0	13	Obama	Obama	NNP	dep	356	PERSON	 (NNP Obama)	1
0	14	Barack	Barack	NNP	dep	356	PERSON	 (NNP Barack)	1
0	15	Obama	Obama	NNP	dep	356	PERSON	 (NNP Obama)	1
0	16	Revised	revise	VBN	dep	356	O	 (VBN Revised)	1
0	17	Schedule	schedule	VB	dep	356	O	 (VB Schedule)	1
0	18	for	for	IN	dep	356	O	 (IN for)	1
0	19	Obama	Obama	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Obama)	1
0	20	Downstate	Downstate	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Downstate)	1
0	21	Town	Town	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Town)	1
0	22	Hall	Hall	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Hall)	1
0	23	Tour	Tour	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Tour)	1
0	24	Wednesday	Wednesday	NNP	dep	356	DATE	 (NNP Wednesday)	1
0	25	August	August	NNP	dep	356	DATE	 (NNP August)	1
0	26	10	10	CD	dep	356	DATE	 (CD 10)	1
0	27	2005	2005	CD	dep	356	DATE	 (CD 2005)	1
0	28	FOR	for	IN	dep	356	O	 (IN FOR)	1
0	29	IMMEDIATE	immediate	JJ	dep	356	O	 (JJ IMMEDIATE)	1
0	30	RELEASE	release	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN RELEASE)	1
0	31	Washington	Washington	NNP	dep	356	LOCATION	 (NNP Washington)	1
0	32	Contact	contact	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN Contact)	1
0	33	Robert	Robert	NNP	dep	356	PERSON	 (NNP Robert)	1
0	34	Gibbs	Gibbs	NNP	dep	356	PERSON	 (NNP Gibbs)	1
0	35	or	or	CC	cc	356	O	 (CC or)	1
0	36	Tommy	Tommy	NNP	dep	356	PERSON	 (NNP Tommy)	1
0	37	Vietor	Vietor	NNP	dep	356	PERSON	 (NNP Vietor)	1
0	38	202	202	CD	dep	356	NUMBER	 (CD 202)	1
0	39	228	228	CD	dep	356	NUMBER	 (CD 228)	1
0	40	5511	5511	CD	dep	356	NUMBER	 (CD 5511)	1
0	41	Illinois	Illinois	NNP	dep	356	LOCATION	 (NNP Illinois)	1
0	42	Contact	contact	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN Contact)	1
0	43	Julian	Julian	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP Julian)	1
0	44	Green	Green	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP Green)	1
0	45	Date	Date	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP Date)	1
0	46	August	August	NNP	dep	356	DATE	 (NNP August)	1
0	47	10	10	CD	dep	356	DATE	 (CD 10)	1
0	48	2005	2005	CD	dep	356	DATE	 (CD 2005)	1
0	49	Revised	revise	VBN	dep	356	O	 (VBN Revised)	2
0	50	Schedule	schedule	VB	dep	356	O	 (VB Schedule)	2
0	51	for	for	IN	dep	356	O	 (IN for)	2
0	52	Obama	Obama	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Obama)	2
0	53	Downstate	Downstate	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Downstate)	2
0	54	Town	Town	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Town)	2
0	55	Hall	Hall	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Hall)	2
0	56	Tour	Tour	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Tour)	2
0	57	WASHINGTON	WASHINGTON	NNP	dep	356	LOCATION	 (NNP WASHINGTON)	2
0	58	The	The	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP The)	2
0	59	first	first	JJ	dep	356	ORDINAL	 (JJ first)	2
0	60	day	day	NN	dep	356	TIME	 (NN day)	2
0	61	of	of	IN	dep	356	O	 (IN of)	2
0	62	Senator	Senator	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP Senator)	2
0	63	Obama	Obama	NNP	dep	356	PERSON	 (NNP Obama)	2
0	64	s	s	VBZ	dep	356	O	 (VBZ s)	2
0	65	D	d	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN D)	2
0	66	IL	il	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN IL)	2
0	67	Downstate	Downstate	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP Downstate)	2
0	68	tour	tour	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN tour)	2
0	69	has	have	VBZ	dep	356	O	 (VBZ has)	2
0	70	been	be	VBN	dep	356	O	 (VBN been)	2
0	71	rescheduled	reschedule	VBN	dep	356	O	 (VBN rescheduled)	2
0	72	to	to	TO	dep	356	O	 (TO to)	2
0	73	October	October	NNP	dep	356	DATE	 (NNP October)	2
0	74	15	15	CD	dep	356	DATE	 (CD 15)	2
0	75	to	to	TO	dep	356	O	 (TO to)	2
0	76	allow	allow	VB	dep	356	O	 (VB allow)	2
0	77	the	the	DT	dep	356	O	 (DT the)	2
0	78	Senator	Senator	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP Senator)	2
0	79	to	to	TO	dep	356	O	 (TO to)	2
0	80	attend	attend	VB	dep	356	O	 (VB attend)	2
0	81	the	the	DT	dep	356	O	 (DT the)	2
0	82	funeral	funeral	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN funeral)	2
0	83	of	of	IN	dep	356	O	 (IN of)	2
0	84	John	John	NNP	dep	356	PERSON	 (NNP John)	2
0	85	H	H	NNP	dep	356	PERSON	 (NNP H)	2
0	86	Johnson	Johnson	NNP	dep	356	PERSON	 (NNP Johnson)	2
0	87	a	a	DT	dep	356	O	 (DT a)	2
0	88	prominent	prominent	JJ	dep	356	O	 (JJ prominent)	2
0	89	Illinoisan	Illinoisan	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP Illinoisan)	2
0	90	Specific	specific	JJ	dep	356	O	 (JJ Specific)	2
0	91	times	time	NNS	dep	356	O	 (NNS times)	2
0	92	and	and	CC	cc	356	O	 (CC and)	2
0	93	locations	location	NNS	dep	356	O	 (NNS locations)	2
0	94	for	for	IN	dep	356	O	 (IN for)	2
0	95	the	the	DT	dep	356	O	 (DT the)	2
0	96	town	town	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN town)	2
0	97	hall	hall	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN hall)	2
0	98	meetings	meeting	NNS	dep	356	O	 (NNS meetings)	2
0	99	will	will	MD	dep	356	O	 (MD will)	2
0	100	be	be	VB	dep	356	O	 (VB be)	3
0	101	released	release	VBN	dep	356	O	 (VBN released)	3
0	102	as	as	RB	dep	356	O	 (RB as)	3
0	103	soon	soon	RB	dep	356	O	 (RB soon)	3
0	104	as	as	IN	dep	356	O	 (IN as)	3
0	105	they	they	PRP	dep	356	O	 (PRP they)	3
0	106	are	be	VBP	dep	356	O	 (VBP are)	3
0	107	available	available	JJ	dep	356	O	 (JJ available)	3
0	108	Events	event	NNS	dep	356	O	 (NNS Events)	3
0	109	on	on	IN	dep	356	O	 (IN on)	3
0	110	Tuesday	Tuesday	NNP	dep	356	DATE	 (NNP Tuesday)	3
0	111	Wednesday	Wednesday	NNP	dep	356	DATE	 (NNP Wednesday)	3
0	112	and	and	CC	cc	356	O	 (CC and)	3
0	113	Thursday	Thursday	NNP	dep	356	DATE	 (NNP Thursday)	3
0	114	will	will	MD	dep	356	O	 (MD will)	3
0	115	not	not	RB	dep	356	O	 (RB not)	3
0	116	change	change	VB	dep	356	O	 (VB change)	3
0	117	REVISED	revise	VBN	dep	356	O	 (VBN REVISED)	3
0	118	DOWNSTATE	downstate	JJ	dep	356	O	 (JJ DOWNSTATE)	3
0	119	TOWN	town	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN TOWN)	3
0	120	HALL	hall	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN HALL)	3
0	121	TOUR	tour	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN TOUR)	3
0	122	SCHEDULE	schedule	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN SCHEDULE)	3
0	123	Tuesday	Tuesday	NNP	dep	356	DATE	 (NNP Tuesday)	3
0	124	August	August	NNP	dep	356	DATE	 (NNP August)	3
0	125	16	16	CD	dep	356	DATE	 (CD 16)	3
0	126	9	9	CD	dep	356	DATE	 (CD 9)	3
0	127	30	30	CD	dep	356	DATE	 (CD 30)	3
0	128	AM	AM	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP AM)	3
0	129	CSTMadison	CSTMadison	NNP	dep	356	LOCATION	 (NNP CSTMadison)	3
0	130	County	County	NNP	dep	356	LOCATION	 (NNP County)	3
0	131	town	town	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN town)	3
0	132	hall	hall	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN hall)	3
0	133	meeting	meeting	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN meeting)	3
0	134	with	with	IN	dep	356	O	 (IN with)	3
0	135	Senator	Senator	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP Senator)	3
0	136	Obama	Obama	NNP	dep	356	PERSON	 (NNP Obama)	3
0	137	Lewis	Lewis	NNP	dep	356	PERSON	 (NNP Lewis)	3
0	138	and	and	CC	cc	356	O	 (CC and)	3
0	139	Clark	Clark	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Clark)	3
0	140	Community	Community	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Community)	3
0	141	College	College	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP College)	3
0	142	The	The	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP The)	3
0	143	Commons	Commons	NNPS	dep	356	O	 (NNPS Commons)	3
0	144	located	located	JJ	dep	356	O	 (JJ located)	3
0	145	in	in	IN	dep	356	O	 (IN in)	3
0	146	the	the	DT	det	356	O	 (DT the)	3
0	147	McPike	McPike	NNP	dep	356	PERSON	 (NNP McPike)	3
0	148	building	building	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN building)	3
0	149	5800	5800	CD	dep	356	DATE	 (CD 5800)	3
0	150	Godfrey	Godfrey	NNP	dep	356	LOCATION	 (NNP Godfrey)	3
0	151	Road	Road	NNP	dep	356	LOCATION	 (NNP Road)	3
0	152	Godfrey	Godfrey	NNP	dep	356	LOCATION	 (NNP Godfrey)	3
0	153	IL	il	NN	dep	356	LOCATION	 (NN IL)	3
0	154	NOON	noon	NN	dep	356	LOCATION	 (NN NOON)	3
0	155	CSTGreene	CSTGreene	NNP	dep	356	LOCATION	 (NNP CSTGreene)	3
0	156	County	County	NNP	dep	356	LOCATION	 (NNP County)	3
0	157	town	town	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN town)	3
0	158	hall	hall	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN hall)	3
0	159	meeting	meeting	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN meeting)	3
0	160	with	with	IN	dep	356	O	 (IN with)	3
0	161	Senator	Senator	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP Senator)	3
0	162	Obama	Obama	NNP	dep	356	PERSON	 (NNP Obama)	3
0	163	Goetten	Goetten	NNP	dep	356	PERSON	 (NNP Goetten)	3
0	164	s	s	VBZ	dep	356	O	 (VBZ s)	3
0	165	Oasis	Oasis	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Oasis)	3
0	166	Route	Route	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Route)	3
0	167	67	67	CD	dep	356	NUMBER	 (CD 67)	3
0	168	just	just	RB	dep	356	O	 (RB just)	3
0	169	south	south	RB	dep	356	O	 (RB south)	3
0	170	of	of	IN	dep	356	O	 (IN of)	3
0	171	downtown	downtown	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN downtown)	3
0	172	Carrollton	Carrollton	NNP	dep	356	LOCATION	 (NNP Carrollton)	3
0	173	Carrollton	Carrollton	NNP	dep	356	LOCATION	 (NNP Carrollton)	3
0	174	IL	il	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN IL)	3
0	175	2	2	CD	dep	356	NUMBER	 (CD 2)	3
0	176	45	45	CD	dep	356	NUMBER	 (CD 45)	3
0	177	PM	pm	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN PM)	3
0	178	CSTPike	CSTPike	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP CSTPike)	3
0	179	County	County	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP County)	3
0	180	town	town	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN town)	3
0	181	hall	hall	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN hall)	3
0	182	meeting	meeting	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN meeting)	3
0	183	with	with	IN	dep	356	O	 (IN with)	3
0	184	Senator	Senator	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP Senator)	3
0	185	Obama	Obama	NNP	dep	356	PERSON	 (NNP Obama)	3
0	186	Crossroads	Crossroads	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP Crossroads)	3
0	187	Center	Center	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP Center)	3
0	188	125	125	CD	dep	356	NUMBER	 (CD 125)	3
0	189	W	W	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP W)	3
0	190	Jefferson	Jefferson	NNP	dep	356	LOCATION	 (NNP Jefferson)	3
0	191	Street	Street	NNP	dep	356	LOCATION	 (NNP Street)	3
0	192	Pittsfield	Pittsfield	NNP	dep	356	LOCATION	 (NNP Pittsfield)	3
0	193	IL	il	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN IL)	3
0	194	5	5	CD	dep	356	NUMBER	 (CD 5)	3
0	195	00	00	CD	dep	356	NUMBER	 (CD 00)	3
0	196	PM	pm	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN PM)	3
0	197	CSTMorgan	CSTMorgan	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP CSTMorgan)	3
0	198	County	County	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP County)	3
0	199	town	town	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN town)	3
0	200	hall	hall	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN hall)	3
0	201	meeting	meeting	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN meeting)	3
0	202	with	with	IN	dep	356	O	 (IN with)	3
0	203	Senator	Senator	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Senator)	3
0	204	Obama	Obama	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Obama)	3
0	205	Jacksonville	Jacksonville	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Jacksonville)	3
0	206	High	High	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP High)	3
0	207	School	School	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP School)	3
0	208	media	media	NNS	dep	356	O	 (NNS media)	3
0	209	center	center	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN center)	3
0	210	1211	1211	CD	dep	356	DATE	 (CD 1211)	3
0	211	North	North	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP North)	3
0	212	Diamond	Diamond	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP Diamond)	3
0	213	Street	Street	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP Street)	3
0	214	Jacksonville	Jacksonville	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP Jacksonville)	3
0	215	IL	il	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN IL)	3
0	216	Wednesday	Wednesday	NNP	dep	356	DATE	 (NNP Wednesday)	3
0	217	August	August	NNP	dep	356	DATE	 (NNP August)	3
0	218	17	17	CD	dep	356	DATE	 (CD 17)	3
0	219	10	10	CD	dep	356	DATE	 (CD 10)	3
0	220	00	00	CD	dep	356	DATE	 (CD 00)	3
0	221	AM	AM	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP AM)	3
0	222	CSTObama	CSTObama	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP CSTObama)	3
0	223	speaks	speak	VBZ	dep	356	O	 (VBZ speaks)	3
0	224	at	at	IN	dep	356	O	 (IN at)	3
0	225	the	the	DT	det	356	O	 (DT the)	3
0	226	County	County	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP County)	3
0	227	Chairmans	Chairmans	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Chairmans)	3
0	228	Association	Association	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Association)	3
0	229	Breakfast	Breakfast	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Breakfast)	3
0	230	Crowne	Crowne	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Crowne)	3
0	231	Plaza	Plaza	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Plaza)	3
0	232	hotel	hotel	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN hotel)	3
0	233	3000	3000	CD	dep	356	NUMBER	 (CD 3000)	3
0	234	S	s	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN S)	3
0	235	Dirksen	Dirksen	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Dirksen)	3
0	236	Parkway	Parkway	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Parkway)	3
0	237	Springfield	Springfield	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Springfield)	3
0	238	IL	il	NN	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NN IL)	3
0	239	AFTERNOONSenator	AFTERNOONSenator	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP AFTERNOONSenator)	3
0	240	Obama	Obama	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Obama)	3
0	241	attends	attend	VBZ	dep	356	O	 (VBZ attends)	3
0	242	Governor	governor	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN Governor)	3
0	243	s	s	NNS	dep	356	O	 (NNS s)	3
0	244	Day	day	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN Day)	3
0	245	at	at	IN	dep	356	O	 (IN at)	3
0	246	the	the	DT	det	356	O	 (DT the)	3
0	247	State	State	NNP	dep	356	LOCATION	 (NNP State)	3
0	248	Fair	Fair	NNP	dep	356	LOCATION	 (NNP Fair)	3
0	249	Springfield	Springfield	NNP	dep	356	LOCATION	 (NNP Springfield)	3
0	250	IL	il	NN	dep	356	LOCATION	 (NN IL)	3
0	251	Thursday	Thursday	NNP	dep	356	DATE	 (NNP Thursday)	3
0	252	August	August	NNP	dep	356	DATE	 (NNP August)	3
0	253	18	18	CD	dep	356	DATE	 (CD 18)	3
0	254	8	8	CD	dep	356	DATE	 (CD 8)	3
0	255	30	30	CD	dep	356	DATE	 (CD 30)	3
0	256	AM	AM	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP AM)	3
0	257	CSTObama	CSTObama	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP CSTObama)	4
0	258	fills	fill	VBZ	dep	356	O	 (VBZ fills)	4
0	259	his	he	PRP$	dep	356	O	 (PRP$ his)	4
0	260	flexible	flexible	JJ	dep	356	O	 (JJ flexible)	4
0	261	fuel	fuel	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN fuel)	4
0	262	vehicle	vehicle	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN vehicle)	4
0	263	with	with	IN	dep	356	O	 (IN with)	4
0	264	E85	E85	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP E85)	4
0	265	Pacific	Pacific	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP Pacific)	4
0	266	Pride	Pride	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP Pride)	4
0	267	3117	3117	CD	dep	356	NUMBER	 (CD 3117)	4
0	268	North	North	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP North)	4
0	269	22nd	22nd	CD	dep	356	NUMBER	 (CD 22nd)	4
0	270	Street	Street	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP Street)	4
0	271	Decatur	Decatur	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP Decatur)	4
0	272	IL	il	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN IL)	4
0	273	9	9	CD	dep	356	NUMBER	 (CD 9)	4
0	274	00	00	CD	dep	356	NUMBER	 (CD 00)	4
0	275	AM	AM	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP AM)	4
0	276	CSTMacon	CSTMacon	NNP	dep	356	LOCATION	 (NNP CSTMacon)	4
0	277	County	County	NNP	dep	356	LOCATION	 (NNP County)	4
0	278	town	town	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN town)	4
0	279	hall	hall	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN hall)	4
0	280	meeting	meeting	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN meeting)	4
0	281	with	with	IN	dep	356	O	 (IN with)	4
0	282	Senator	Senator	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Senator)	4
0	283	Obama	Obama	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Obama)	4
0	284	Richland	Richland	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Richland)	4
0	285	Community	Community	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Community)	4
0	286	College	College	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP College)	4
0	287	shilling	shill	VBG	dep	356	O	 (VBG shilling)	4
0	288	salon	salon	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN salon)	4
0	289	One	one	CD	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (CD One)	4
0	290	College	College	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP College)	4
0	291	Park	Park	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Park)	4
0	292	Decatur	Decatur	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Decatur)	4
0	293	IL	il	NN	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NN IL)	4
0	294	11	11	CD	dep	356	NUMBER	 (CD 11)	4
0	295	00	00	CD	dep	356	NUMBER	 (CD 00)	4
0	296	AM	AM	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP AM)	4
0	297	CSTDouglas	CSTDouglas	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP CSTDouglas)	4
0	298	County	County	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP County)	4
0	299	town	town	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN town)	4
0	300	hall	hall	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN hall)	4
0	301	meeting	meeting	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN meeting)	4
0	302	with	with	IN	dep	356	O	 (IN with)	4
0	303	Senator	Senator	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP Senator)	4
0	304	Obama	Obama	NNP	dep	356	PERSON	 (NNP Obama)	4
0	305	Las	Las	NNP	dep	356	PERSON	 (NNP Las)	4
0	306	Recipe	Recipe	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP Recipe)	4
0	307	banquet	banquet	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN banquet)	4
0	308	room	room	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN room)	4
0	309	125	125	CD	dep	356	NUMBER	 (CD 125)	4
0	310	W	W	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP W)	4
0	311	Sale	Sale	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP Sale)	4
0	312	Street	Street	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP Street)	4
0	313	Tuscola	Tuscola	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP Tuscola)	4
0	314	IL	il	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN IL)	4
0	315	1	1	CD	dep	356	NUMBER	 (CD 1)	4
0	316	00	00	CD	dep	356	NUMBER	 (CD 00)	4
0	317	PM	pm	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN PM)	4
0	318	CSTChampaign	CSTChampaign	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP CSTChampaign)	4
0	319	County	County	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP County)	4
0	320	town	town	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN town)	4
0	321	hall	hall	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN hall)	4
0	322	meeting	meeting	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN meeting)	4
0	323	Illinois	Illinois	NNP	dep	356	LOCATION	 (NNP Illinois)	4
0	324	terminal	terminal	JJ	dep	356	O	 (JJ terminal)	4
0	325	4th	4th	JJ	dep	356	ORDINAL	 (JJ 4th)	4
0	326	floor	floor	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN floor)	4
0	327	45	45	CD	dep	356	NUMBER	 (CD 45)	4
0	328	E	e	NN	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NN E)	4
0	329	University	University	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP University)	4
0	330	Champaign	Champaign	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Champaign)	4
0	331	IL	il	NN	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NN IL)	4
0	332	3	3	CD	dep	356	NUMBER	 (CD 3)	4
0	333	00	00	CD	dep	356	NUMBER	 (CD 00)	4
0	334	PM	pm	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN PM)	4
0	335	CSTVermillion	CSTVermillion	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP CSTVermillion)	4
0	336	County	County	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP County)	4
0	337	town	town	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN town)	4
0	338	hall	hall	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN hall)	4
0	339	meeting	meeting	NN	dep	356	O	 (NN meeting)	4
0	340	with	with	IN	dep	356	O	 (IN with)	4
0	341	Senator	Senator	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Senator)	4
0	342	Obama	Obama	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Obama)	4
0	343	Danville	Danville	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Danville)	4
0	344	Area	Area	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Area)	4
0	345	Community	Community	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Community)	4
0	346	College	College	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP College)	4
0	347	Vermillion	Vermillion	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Vermillion)	4
0	348	Hall	Hall	NNP	dep	356	ORGANIZATION	 (NNP Hall)	4
0	349	Room	Room	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP Room)	4
0	350	306	306	CD	dep	356	NUMBER	 (CD 306)	4
0	351	2000	2000	CD	dep	356	DATE	 (CD 2000)	4
0	352	East	East	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP East)	4
0	353	Main	Main	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP Main)	4
0	354	Street	Street	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP Street)	4
0	355	Danville	Danville	NNP	dep	356	O	 (NNP Danville)	4
0	356	IL	il	NN	root	0	O	 (NN IL))	4

